You know how your coffee can got
smaller, and they were all "sorry, prices
are crazy right now"?
Yeah —
coffee prices just crashed to a nineteen-month
low.
Nobody's talking about it.
Like, the entire excuse is gone.
It left.
And the can?
The can just...
stayed small.
Never went back.
And look —
I stare at numbers all day for
my job, and I built the biggest
free shrinkflation database anybody's put online, so
I'm in this stuff constantly.
So believe me when I tell you:
if you've ever been standing in your
kitchen counting out scoops, trying to stretch
a can to payday, feeling a little
cheap about it?
That's not a you thing.
They set it up that way.
On purpose.
Here, look at this.
The big can used to be fifty-one
ounces.
Fifty-one!
Now?
Forty-three and a half.
That's almost fifteen percent of your coffee
that just...
isn't there anymore.
And here's the part that actually gets
me —
coffee did hit an all-time high in
early 2025, sure.
But it's fallen almost forty percent since.
So here's where they got you —
and honestly it's kind of genius, in
an evil way.
The price per pot crept up, but
the number on the front of the
can barely moved.
So nobody notices.
And economists have an actual name for
this —
"rockets and feathers." Prices shoot up like
a rocket...
and float down like a feather.
Real slow.
If they come down at all.
So the costs left, the shrink stayed,
and you basically gave them a permanent
raise.
So tell me in the comments —
is your coffee shrinking too?
Because I need to know it's not
just me.
Follow me while I catch the next
one.
And whatever you drink in the morning?
Look it up at fullcarts.org.