okay so I just caught folders
um these guys quietly made your coffee can smaller
and the whole time they're like oh
prices are so high right now
well yeah
coffee just crashed to a 19 month low
and nobody's even talking about it
oh and by the way
a new series is called caught uh
where I find the companies quietly shrinking your stuff
and I catch them in the act
but what do I know
I'm just a tired dad who's sick of getting ripped off
so I went and build the biggest
free shrinkflation database I know of
and uh
here's the thing that gets me
if you've ever stood in your kitchen
like counting out scoops
trying to stretch a can till payday
or kind of just feeling a little cheap about it all
no
that's not you uh
they did that on purpose and here
I mean look at this
the big can used to be 51 ounces
and now just 43 and a half
that's literally almost what
15% of your coffee just gone
and get this like
coffee hit an all time high back in uh
2025 and it's dropped almost 40% since
so watch what they did the price per pot crept up
while the big number on the front of the hand
it barely moved so you don't clock it at all
and there's actually a name for this
and I'm not even making this up
economists call it rockets
and feathers where prices go up like a rocket
and they come down like a feather real slow
if they ever come down at all
so yeah
well the cost left
the shrinks stayed
and you basically gave folders a permanent race
so tell me in the comments below
if your coffee's been drinking too
I honestly just need to know that it's not just me
so follow so you can catch me in the next one
and go look up whatever you drink at full cost dot org
see ya